

Vishal Adhikari

- Ahmedabad India
- 8490082929
- vansh.adhikari143@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Results-driven sales performer with solid history of success in bringing in new customers, managing revenue streams and maintaining solid account relationships. Skilled Sales Expert with 6 years career experience in customer satisfaction and interaction. Persuasive negotiation and program management abilities.

Skills

- Sales
- Sales Goals
- Cross-Selling

- Sales Reporting
- Prospecting Clients
- Direct Sales

Work History

10.2021 - Current

Fashion Consultant

Jack & Jones - Ahmedabad, India

- Assisting in driving sales through targeted product presentation and merchandising.
- Developing relationships with clothing vendors and store operators.
- Greeting all customers cheerfully and asked open-ended questions to ascertain needs.
- Maintained knowledge of current styles and trends to promote clientrelations and grow company presence.
- Providing strong service to customers and increasing customer loyalty.
- Advising clients on ill-fitting or unsuitable clothing and sharing suggestions to enhance the finished product.

03.2020 - 10.2021

Sales Officer

ZUDIO TRENT LIMITED - Ahmedabad, India

- Strengthened merchandising and promotional strategies to drive customer engagement and boost sales.
- Kept orderly and accurate accounting records by monitoring sales documentation.
- Maintained company's visual merchandise standards through general housekeeping and planograms.
- Offered hands-on assistance to customers, assessing needs and maintaining current knowledge of consumer preferences.

04.2018 - 12.2019

Sales Consultant

Concept Hyundai - Ahmedabad, India

- Improved sales by managing sales lifecycle from lead generation through contract negotiations and closings.
- Negotiated purchase prices and explained sales, warranty and optional products.
- Met customers on lot and in showroom to discuss available vehicles and options.
- Reviewed vehicles before final delivery to validate for completed tasks such as installed add-ons and damage corrections.

07.2017 - 04.2018

Relationship Manager

Exide Life Insurance - Ahmedabad, India

- Generated new business and referral clients in partnership with financial advisors and branch team.
- Communicated regularly with clients to understand needs, evaluate current product use and cross-sell new products.
- Developed summaries to assess each client's participation level and determine targets for follow-up plans.
- Worked with clients to address and respond to client and partnership management issues.
- Built and maintained relationships with new and existing clients while providing high level of expertise.

11.2016 - 05.2017

Customer Service Representative

Shott Amusement - Ahmedabad, India

- Provided primary customer support to internal and external customers.
- Assisted customers with setting appointments, special order requests, and arranging merchandise pick-up.
- Liaised with customers, management and sales team to better understand customer needs and recommend appropriate solutions.
- Collected customer feedback and made process changes to exceed customer satisfaction goals.

Education

04/2018

Bachelors of Commerce, Accounting, Gujarat Commerce College - Ahmedabad

03/2015

High School Diploma, Swaminarayan Vidhyamandir High School - Ahmedabad

Languages

Gujarati, Hindi: Native language

English: B

Upper intermediate